<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>



    <string name="grid_help_free">
        Desktop Grid\n\n
        - Rows/Columns:  Sets the number of Rows and Columns on the Desktop.  (this is restricted to +/- 1 from the device
        default in the Free version.  Pro allows selecting 2-12 for each.)\n
        - Hide Dock: Hides the Dock.  This option is always set for configurations with icons smaller than 28dp.\n
        - Allow Landscape: Allows the Launcher to rotate into Landscape.  This is the default on Tablets.  It can be set on Phones
        but doing so may not work well and is not supported.\n
        - Reset Default: Sets all values, including Icon Sizes, to the Device Default.\n
        \n\n
        Icon Sizes\n\n
        - Use Calculated Sizes:  Resets just the Icon and Icon Text sizes to the Device Default.\n
        - Percent slider:  Allows changing the icon size.  Text does not change using this.  Note that 100% is the calculated ideal
        size for the device.  Settings over 100% may result in truncated icons and is not supported.  (Values up to 110% may be fine
        in most configurations, especially if you don\'t use folders.)\n
         - (Pro Only) Adjust Values: Swaps the Percent Slider for a UI allowing more fine tuned icon and text values.  (not restricted to 75-125%)\n
        \n
        (This Dialog will only appear once.  You can access it again from Help in the Menu.)\n
    </string>

     <string name="grid_help_pro">
        Desktop Grid\n\n
        - Rows/Columns:  Sets the number of Rows and Columns on the Desktop.  Values can be set between 2 and 12 of each.\n
        - Hide Dock: Hides the Dock.  This option is always set for configurations with icons smaller than 28dp.\n
        - Allow Landscape: Allows the Launcher to rotate into Landscape.  This is the default on Tablets.  It can be set on Phones
        but doing so may not work well and is not supported.\n
        - Reset Default: Sets all values, including Icon Sizes, to the Device Default.\n
        \n\n
        Icon Sizes\n\n
        - Use Calculated Sizes:  Resets just the Icon and Icon Text sizes to the Device Default.\n
        - Percent slider:  Allows changing the icon size.  Text does not change using this.  Note that 100% is the calculated ideal
        size for the device.  Settings over 100% may result in truncated icons and is not supported.  (Values up to 110% may be fine
        in most configurations, especially if you don\'t use folders.)\n
         - Adjust Values: Swaps the Percent Slider for a UI allowing more fine tuned icon and text values.  (not restricted to 75-125%)\n
         \n
         (This Dialog will only appear once.  You can access it again from Help in the Menu.)\n
    </string>


</resources>